Hoffman Family Papers
© 2006 University of Connecticut
- Series V: Newspaper and Periodical Clippings, undated, 1936-1997
  - News, 1969, [1. Paul Levine, "(illegible) Urges Yippiedom for Miami," unknown, Hoffman visits Miami during Chicago 7 trial; 2. unknown, "Yippie Leader Freed," unknown, charges dismissed in weapons and drug possession case; 3. Abbie Hoffman, "The Doctor Revolt," WIN Magazine, problems with hospitals and the medical community; 4. Philip F. Murphy, "Abbie Hoffman Is Home, City Remains Undaunted," Worcester Telegram, Hoffman is back is Worcester after Democratic National Convention; 5. unknown, "Ideas In Action: Revolutionary Gurus," Time Magazine, discussion of Guevara, Marcuse, Debray, Fanon, and Mao; 6. Marty Jezer, "Review of Revolution for The Hell of It," Liberation Magazine, review of Hoffman's book; 7. J. Anthony Lukas, "Go on Trial Today in Another Round in 1968 Chicago Convention (illegible)," New York Times, Chicago 7 trial; 8. Emanuel Perlmutter, "Lawyers' Rally to Assail Jailing," New York Times, lawyers protest jailing of two defense attorneys; 9. Jerry Tallmer, "The Chicago Eight - A Colorful Cast," New York Post, description of defendents; 10. J. Anthony Lukas, "Judge Drops Contempt Citations Against 4 Defending the Chicago 8," New York Times, charges against lawyers dropped; 11. Jerry Tallmer, "2 Jurors at Chicago 8 Trial Get Threat," New York Post, two female jurors receive threatening letters; 12. J. Anthony Lukas, "Judge Orders Arrest of 4 Defense Attorneys as Trial Begins for Leaders of '68 Chicago Demonstrations," New York Times, description of first day of hearings; 13. J. Anthony Lukas, "'Chicago Eight' Challenge the Law on Agitation," New York Times, review of legal case against Chicago 8; 14. Jerry Tallmer, "Chicago Eight Defense Raps Juror's Ouster," New York Post, defense angered over dismissal of jurors; 15. unknown, "Jail Dellinger For Outburst," unknown, Dave Dellinger jailed for courtroom outburst; 16. Jerry Tallmer, "2 new 'Jerry Rubins' Pop Up at Riot Trial," New York Post, others claim to be who the police thought was Jerry Rubin; 17. Raymond R. Coffey, "Cop's Memory is Challenged At Chi 8 Trial," New York Post, defense examines prosecution's star witness; 18. Raymond R. Coffey, "Chi 8 Defense Finds Going Hard," New York Post, no success in discrediting star witness; 19. William Barry Furlong, "A controversial trial tests the limits of dissent," LIFE Magazine, discussion of Chicago 8 trial; 20. Raymond R. Coffey, "Chi 8 Ask Recess For Moratorium," New York Post, permission for defendents to participate in the anti-war moratorium; 21. J. Anthony Lukas, "'Party' Disrupts Chicago 8 Court," New York Times, party for Bobby Seale disrupts proceedings; 22. Tom Wicker, "In The Nation: On Trial in Chicago," New York Times, impressions of the trial; 23. J. Anthony Lukas, "Rubin Surrenders After He Leaves Trial," New York Times, Rubin is jailed after leaving courtroom; 24. n/a, n/a, Sunday Herald Traveler, advertisement for a show in Boston; 25. n/a, n/a, unknown, advertisment for Hoffman speech with Leonard Weinglass and Gerald Lefcourt; 26. John Leonard, "Books of The Times," New York Times, reivew of Counterblast and The Interior Landscape; 26. The Worcester Punch, Vol. 3 No. 5 December 1969; 27. Manasha Bilsey, "The Conspiracy Comes Home: Abbie & Frank," The Worcester Punch, interview with Hoffman concerning trial; 28. J. Anthony Lucas (sic), "Chicago 7 Trial Hears City Aide," New York Times, city aide testifies about the plans of violence; 29. Henrys Resnik, "The Groovy Revolution," Saturday Review, reviews of Woodstock Nation, The Free People, and The Making of a Counter Culture; 30. J. Anthony Lukas, "Judge Is Assailed In Chicago Trial," New York Times, Dellinger accuses Hoffman of denying them a fair trial; 31. Arnold Markowitz, "Radical's Parents Endure Own Trial But Stand By Him," Miami Herald, Rennie Davis' parent support him during trial; 32. J. Anthony Lukas, "Yippies' Leader Tells the Judge Just What His 'Party' Believes" New York Times; Hoffman testifies (two copies); 33. J. Anthony Lukas, "Defendant in Trial of Chicago 7 Calls the Judge 'Very Unfair'", New York Times, Dellinger accuses Judge Hoffman of being partial along with trial proceedings; 34. J. Anthony Lukas, "Attorneys Clash on 'Yippie Myths'," New York Times, Hoffman testifies.] (Box 8:175)
  - News, 1970 January - February, [1. Anthony Lewis, "Breeding Contempt for Law," New York Times, editorial in favor of the Chicago 7; 2. unknown, unknown, New York Times Magazine, summary of trial procedings; 3. unknown, "Federal Judge Sentences Four For Contempt in Chicago Trial," New York Times, events during the sentencing for contempt of court; 4. unknown, "Appeals Court Grants Bail to 'Chicago Seven'", Miami Herald, Hoffman and co-defendents out on bond; 5. Robert Levey, "Chicago 7 lawyer asks probe," Boston Globe, Weinglass request probe into case to determine if it was in contempt of the American judicial system; 6. unknown, "'Chicago Seven' Lawyers Appeal Denial of Bonds," Miami Herald, lawyers appeal ruling on bond; 7. Elliot Cohen, "Judge Hoffman's Brand of Justice," unknown; letter to the editor against Hoffman; 8. unknown, "5 Get Prison Terms In Chicago Riot Case," unknown, sentences and reactions; 9. unknown, "Chicago and the System," unknown, the system proved itself to be fair and the defendents childish; 10. editorial staff; "Repression and The Chicago Eight," Ramparts, defense of the Chicago 8 and state repression; 11. Paul Glusman, "Behind the Chicago Conspiracy Trial," Ramparts, analysis of the trial; 12. J. Anthony Lukas, "Yippie Film on 1968 Convention Is Kept From Jury," New York Times, Judge Hoffman declines to allow video of Yippies in trial; 13. A.H. Weiler, "Yippy For the Yippies," unknown, Hoffman to make a movie; 14. J. Anthony Lukas, "Chicago 7 Cleared of Plot; 5 Guilty on Second Count," New York Times, details of the sentencing; 15. J. Anthony Lukas, "Disorder Erupts at Chicago Trial After Judge Jails a Defendant for Using a Vulgarity," New York Times, Dellinger jailed for vulgarity; 16. unknown; "Davis of Chicago 7 Predicts They'll Be Jailed for Contempt," New York Post, Davis reflects on trial; 17. unknown, "Appeal Hinted In the Jailing of Dellinger," New York Post, Weinglass to appeal Dellinger's sentence; 18. Associated Press, "Dellinger Jailed in Chicago Trial," unknown, Dellinger jailed for vulgarity; 19. J. Anthony Lukas, "Prosecution Says Chicago 7 Planned a Revolution," New York Times, the prosecution's final arguments; 20. J. Anthony Lukas, "Chicago 7 Defense Charges U.S. Concocted Case to Justify Police Violence," New York Times, the defense's closing arguments; 21. J. Anthony Lukas, "Daley on Stand in Chicago Today; Defense Plans an Indictment," New York Times, Daley to take the witness stand; 22. Raymond R. Coffey, "The Chicago Seven: An Unlikely Landmark," New York Post Magazine, analysis of the trial; 23. J. Anthony Lukas, "U.S. Judge Orders Contempt Terms in Chicago Trial," New York Times, sentencing of four for contempt of court; 24. combined services, ""entence of 4 of Chi 7 for Contempt," Sunday News, report of court following the setencing; 25. Marty Jezer, "Reviews: Woodstock Nation," WIN Magazine, review of Woodstock Nation; 26. J. Anthony Lukas, "'Incredible End to an Incredible Trial'," New York Times, analysis and reflection on trial; 27. Pete Hamill, "Chicago Tragedy," New York Post Magazine, condemnation of Judge Hoffman; 28. J. Anthony Lukas, "Kunstler Given Four-Year Term By Chicago Judge," New York Times, sentencing for contempt of court by Judge Hoffman (two copies); 29. Associated Press, "Lawyer for Chicago 7 Gets 4-Year Term for Contempt," Long Island Press, contempt of court sentences; 30. Lee Dembart, "Chicago 7 Jury in Third Day," New York Post, jury deliberations; 31. Harriet Van Horne, "A Pair of Hoffmans," New York Post, editorial critical of Hoffman and Judge Hoffman; 32. United Press International, "Chicago 7 Lawyer Draws Four Years," New York Daily News, contempt of court sentences; 33. Associated Press, "Chicago Jurors Out; Lawyers Sentenced," Newsday, contempt of court sentences; 34. Pete Hamill, "The Chicago Trial," New York Post, editorial on Judge Hoffman; 35. J. Anthony Lukas, "Chicago 7 Cleared of Plot, 5 Guilty on Second Count," New York Times, jury verdict; 36. J. Anthony Lukas, "Jury for Chicago 7 Ends Its Third Day Without a Verdict," New York Times, jury deliberations; 37. Ralph Blumenthal, "New Haven Foils a Bombing Plot," New York Times, five arrested for bombing plot in New Haven; 38. United Press International, "5 of Chicago 7 Guilty on 1 Rap," New York Daily News, jury verdict; 39. United Press International, "'Chicago 7' Acquitted of Conspiracy," The Boston Globe, jury verdict; 40. John Kifner, "Chicago 7 Jurors Tell of Compromise," New York Times, information on jury deliberations; 41. United Press International, "Chicago 7 Attorneys Map Appeal Tactics," New York Daily News, defense appeals convictions; 42. unknown, "Chicago 5 Sentenced: 5 Years, $5000 Fines," Record American, photograph of Ms. Hoffman and Ms. Rubin outside the courtroom in protest of sentence; 43. Tom Topor, "Chi Protests Across Country," New York Post, protests against sentences; 44. J. Anthony Lukas, "5 in Chicago Trial Get 5-Year Terms and $5,000 Fines," New York Times, sentencing of defendents; 45. (illegible) Times Service, "(illegible) Chicago Trial (illegible) Terms, Fines," Worcester Telegram, sentencing of defendents; 46. Associated Press, "ABA Unit to Probe Court Proceedings," Worcester Telegram, American Bar Association probe into trial; 47. William Chapman, "'Chicago 5' Draws 5-Year Jail Terms," The Boston Globe, sentencing of defendents; 48. Liberation News Service, "'Sure We're In Contempt'," The Punch, radical perspective on the Chicago 7 trial; 49. unknown, "The Dissent-Establishment Gap Grows Wider," Sunday News, analysis of the trial; 50. Tom Wicker, "In The Nation: Who Can Question the Government?," New York Times, condemnation of Judge Hoffman's conduct in the trial; 51. unknown, "The Chicago Trial: A Loss for All," Time Magazine, condemnation of Judge Hoffman's conduct in the trial (original with one copy); 52. Kay S. Richards, "Chicago 7: A Trial for Jury, Too," The Boston Globe, discussion of the jury; 53. James W. Singer, "Congressional petitions ask '7' bail," Chicago Sun-Times, developments after the trial; 54. John Kifner, "Ex-U.S. Aides Urge Bonds in Chicago," New York Times, developments following trial; 55. Kay S. Richards, "How I Felt Facing The Chicago Seven," New York Post, personal reflections on the Chicago 7 trial; 56. John Kifner, "Supporter of 7 Fight Back Tears," New York Times, reaction to verdict; 57. United Press International, "Federal Prosecutor Criticizes the Chicago 7 Defendants and Their Lawyers," New York Times, U.S. Attorney General James Foran denounces Chicago 7; 58. unknown, "Chicago 7 Protest in Washington Ends With 112 Youths Arrested," New York Times, details of protest; 59. J. Anthony Lukas, "5 In Chicago Trial Get 5-Year Terms and $5,000 Fines," New York Times, appeals and sentencing.] (Box 8:176)
  - News, 1970 March - December, [1. Jack Hoffman, "We Have Problems of Injustice in America, Too," unknown, letter to the editor about unfair trials; 2. Tony Fuller, "'Chicago 7' Released Pending Appeal," The Boston Globe, defendents released on bond; 3. n/a, n/a, unknown, advertisement for William O. Douglas' book Points of Rebellion; 4. n/a, n/a, New York Times, editorial page from March 3, 1970; 5. D.J.R. Bruckner, "Treat Violence As Crime, Not Political Issue," Miami Herald, editorial; 6. J. Anthony Lukas, "The Second Confrontation In Chicago," New York Times Magazine, reflections on sentencing; 7. Martin I. Gross, "'Revolution' Has Become Giant Put-On Of The Era," Miami Herald, editorial critical of the New Left; 8. Richard Flacks and Milton Mankoff, "Why They Burned the Bank," The Nation, analysis of revolt in Santa Barbara; 9. unknown, "The Seven," unknown, article in support of the Chicago 7; 10. Gene Marine, "Chicago," The Rolling Stone, reflections on the Chicago 7 trial; 11. United Press International, "Rice Closes, Bars Hoffman," unknown, Rice University bars Hoffman from speaking; 12. Associated Press, "'Chicago 7' Speech Killed," Miami Herald, Rice University bars Hoffman from speaking; 13. unknown, "Abbie Hoffman's Talk May Be Shifted to HC," unknown, Hoffman to speak at Holy Cross College; 14. unknown, "Hoffman Is Heard By 2,000 at HC," Worcester Telegram, Hoffman's speech at Holy Cross (three copies); 15. n/a, n/a, The Rolling Stone, page 17 of April 16th 1970 paper; 16. Associated Press, "Abbie Gets the Gate At White House Tea," unknown, Hoffman denied entrance to White House with Grace Slick; 17. United Press International, "Slicked-up Abby Denied Entry to Tricia's Tea," The News, Framingham-Natick, Hoffman denied entrance to White House with Grace Slick; 18. unknown, "Abbie Gets a Passport," unknown; editorial against Hoffman's visit to Cuba 19. David Newman and Robert Benton, "(illegible) Sex Figures," unknown, Hoffman named in article; 20. Sick, Vol. 10 No. 6, September 1970; 21. Paul Laikin and Jerry Grandenetti, "Abbie Hoffman's Charm School," Sick, cartoon story in support of Abbie; 22. n/a, n/a, National Lampoon, front cover of October 1970 issue.] (Box 8:177)
  - News, 1971, [1. Fred P. Graham, "Chaos Over the Issue of Its Abuse," New York Times Magazine, debate over the flag shirt; 2. Associated Press, "Lawmaker Is Criticized For Tax-on-Sex Bill," unknown, Rep. Bernard C. Gladstone introduce joke legislation; 3. James A. Gourgouras, "Main Street," The Evening Gazette (Worcester), article listing upcoming events, mentions Jack Hoffman; 4. Norman Fruchter, unknown, Liberation, the efficacy of protest; 5. Norman Fruchter, "Games in the Arena: Movement Propaganda and the Culture of the Spectacle," Liberation, the media and the movement; 6. Associated Press, "Hoffman indicted, Mitchell sued as ripples spread from Mayday protests," unknown, arrests following the Mayday demonstration; 7. Associated Press, "Abbie Hoffman Is Indicted In Washington," Worcester Telegram, charges against Hoffman; 8. unknown, "The erosion of legal rights," The Boston Globe, editorial against government violation of privacy rights (two copies); 9. Russell Baker, "The Dumbest Rip-Off," New York Times, against Hoffman cheating the phone company; 10. Dotson Rader, Steal This Book, New York Times, review of Steal This Book (two copies); 11. n/a, n/a, The Phoenix, letter to the editor against Hoffman; 12. n/a, n/a, unknown, page of People, etc. with a section on Hoffman; 13. Bob Williams, "Network Newsmen Spurn Ch. 13 Show With Abbie," New York Post, interview falls through; 14. J. Anthony Lukas, "Bobby Seale's Birthday Cake (Oh, Far Out!)," New York Times Magazine, reflections on the Chicago 7; 15. Bruce McCabe, "Steal This Story Or, Abbie Hoffman in Beantown," Boston Sunday Globe, reflections on Abbie Hoffman.] (Box 8:178)
  - News, 1972, [1. unknown, "(illegible) fuses people together," unknown; soldier's reflections on Vietnam; 2. unknown, unknown, unknown, short piece on oil and taxes; 3. Daniel St. Albin Greene, "Watergate Boggles Abbie," New York Times, interview with Hoffman; 4. Kenneth D. Campbell, "Fontainebleau, sand and Abbie Hoffman," The Boston Globe, Hoffman and the Republican National Convention; 5. n/a, n/a, unknown, advertisement for Emile de Antonio's Millhouse; 6. n/a, n/a, unknown, editorial page; 7. n/a, n/a, unknown, advertisement for Jack Hoffman for the Chisholm Slate; 8. n/a, n/a, unknown, advertisement for Jack Hoffman for the Chisholm Slate; 9. n/a, n/a, unknown, advertisement for Steal This Book 10. unknown, unknown, unknown, analysis of opinions on the 1972 Presidental elections; 11. Jimmy Breslin, "Alan the Delegate views Nixon," Boston Evening Globe, reflections on the Nixon canidacy; 12. Herbert Black, "MGH studies hospital electical mishaps," Boston Sunday Globe, concerns over hospital electrical accidents are unfounded; 13. Nicholas von Hoffman, "Agnew soft on media that's been soft on (illegible)," The Boston Globe, problems with indefinite jailings; 14. John Kifner, "Freed Chicago Conspiracy' Men Still Active in Protest Roles," Boston Record, current activities of the Chicago 7.] (Box 8:179)
  - News, 1973, [1. William E. Farrell, "Once More, With Decorum," unknown, developments after the trial; 2. unknown, "Reappearance of a Yippie," unknown, arrest of Hoffman; 3. M.A. Farber, "Abbie Hoffman Fights Defining of Cocaine as Narcotic," New York Times, trial procedings; 4. unknown, "Hoffman Bid Denied in Narcotics Case," New York Times, trial procedings; 5. Associated Press, "U.S. Drops the Charges Against 5 of Chicago 7," New York Times, charges dropped; 6. United Press International, "Chicago Bid Denied," New York Times, judge rejects motion to throw out contempt of court charges; 7. unknown, unknown, unknown, Ms. Hoffman's 90th birthday; 8. unknown, "Smile Abbie!," unknown, Hoffman gets a vasectomy; 9. Linda Greenhouse, "Abbie Hoffman Among 4 Held On Charges of Selling Cocaine," New York Times, arrest on cocaine charges; 10. Ronald Smothers, "Abbie Hoffman Is Held in $200,000 Bail on Cocaine-Sale Charge," New York Times, charges against Hoffman (two copies); 11. unknown; "Hoffman is Accused of Drug Possession," New York Times, charges against Hoffman; 12. unknown; "Hoffman is Named in New Indictments," New York Times, charges against Hoffman; 13. Charles Kaiser, "A 'Routine' Cocaine Bust," Rolling Stone, reflections on the arrest of Hoffman; 14. William E. Farrell, "Chicago 7 Start New Trial Today," New York Times, new contempt of court hearing (three copies); 15. William E. Farrell, unknown, New York Times, procedings of the new trial; 16. William E. Farrell, "Dismissal Asked By Chicago Seven," New York Times, defense asks for a dismissal; 17. United Press International, "Judge Acquits Them on 18 of 38 Contempt Counts," New York Times, verdict in new trial; 18. United Press International, "Bobby Seale Testifies Quietly For Chicago Seven Defendants," New York Times, Seale's testimony; 19. Reuters, "Chicago 7 Lawyers Freed of 7 Charges," New York Times, verdict in new trial; 20. Seth S. King, "Courtroom Calm at Chicago Trial," New York Times, analysis of new Chicago 7 trial; 21. United Press International, "Liddy Cited at Contempt Trial for 5 of Chicago 7," New York Times, involvement of G. Gordon Liddy in survellience during the Democratic National Convention; 22. Associated Press, "Defense Motions Denied In Riot Conspiracy Trial," New York Times, motion to throw out all contempt of courts is denied; 23. Associated Press, "Convict Kunstler & 3 Of Contempt a 2d (sic) Time," unknown, verdict in contempt of court trial (two copies); 24. Andrew H. Malcolm, "Kunstler and 3 Others Found in Contempt at 'Chicago 7' Trial," New York Times, verdict in contempt of court trial (three copies); 25. Andrew H. Malcolm, "Four In Contempt are Spared Jail," New York Times, sentencing in contempt of court trial (two copies).] (Box 8:180)
  - News, 1974, [1. unknown, "John Hoffman, Company Owner," unknown; obiturary for Mr. Hoffman (three copies); 2. unknown, "John Hoffman," The Probian, obiturary for Mr. Hoffman; 3. Clark Whelton, "Dear Abbie," unknown, Hoffman becomes a fugitive; 4. Mike Pearl and Sheila Moran, "Abbie Hoffman Jumps Bail," New York Post, Hoffman becomes a fugitive; 5. Ellen Fleysher, "Hoffman Snubs Court," unknown, Hoffman becomes a fugitive (two copies); 6. unknown, unknown, unknown, reflections on Hoffman; 7. Anita Hoffman, "Good-bye To All That - Abbie Splits," WIN Magazine, reflections on Hoffman; 8. unknown, unknown, unknown, reflections on Hoffman; 9. unknown, "Abbie Hoffman Still At Large," unknown, Hoffman goes underground; 10. Worcester Telegram August 9th 1974; 11. Ronald Smothers, "Abbie Hoffman Is Held in $200,000 Bail on Cocaine-Sale Charge," New York Times, charges against Hoffman; 12. unknown, unknown, Newsweek, Ms. Hoffman comments on Hoffman's move to the underground; 13. Associated Press, "Plea for Dismissal Heard Despite Hoffman's Absence," Worcester Telegram, trial procedings; 14. Ron Rosenbaum, "The Abbie Hoffman Bust: Was It The Real Thing?," The Village Voice, questions surrounding the arrest of Hoffman (two copies); 15. Ron Rosenbaum, "The Abbie Hoffman Bust: The Mystery Deepens," The Village Voice, questions surrounding the arrest of Hoffman (two copies).] (Box 8:181)
  - News, 1975, [1. Robert Bazell, "Abbie's 3d 'Wife' OK With 2d," unknown, Hoffman appears on television to discuss the underground; 2. Ken Kelley, "Riding the Underground Range With Abbie," Playboy, interview about the underground; 3. n/a, n/a, unknown, advertisment for appearance on WNET/Channel 13; 4. John J. O'Connor, "TV: On Abbie Hoffman," New York Times, reflections on Hoffman's use of the media (three copies); 5. Kay Gardella, "Fugitive Abbie Hoffman Interviewed Tonight at 9," unknown, reflections on Hoffman's appearance on WNET/Channel 13; 6. Dick Brass, "Abbie Hoffman- Alive & on TV," New York Post, reflections on Hoffman's appearance on WNET/Channel 13; 7. Associated Press, "Hoffman Discusses the Fugitive Life," Worcester Telegram, reflections on Hoffman's appearance on WNET/Channel 13; 8. Ron Rosenbaum, "A rendezvous with Abbie Hoffman and other notes from the underground," New Times, collection of interviews with Hoffman about the underground (two parts); 9. Stew Albert, "Watching the Abbie Show," WIN Magazine, reflections on Hoffman's television appearances; 10. Abbie Hoffman, "A Note From the Underground To Uncle Sam, From Abbie Hoffman, Fugitive," New York Times, Hoffman's letter to the FBI requesting his file through FOIA; 11. Associated Press, "Radical on the Run - He Poses as Oilman, Has 3 Nose Changes," unknown, Hoffman's activities in the underground; 12. Jeff Nightbyrd, "On the Run," Austin Sun, interview with Hoffman about the underground (two copies).] (Box 8:182)
  - News, 1976, [1. Congressional Quarterly Almanac, Vol. XXXII 1976 pgs. 303-308; 2. Ken Kelley, "Riding the Underground Range with Abbie," Playboy, interview with Hoffman about life underground; 3. Playboy, "Playboy Interview: Abbie Hoffman," Playboy, Hoffman reflects on his life and his activism (three copies); 4. Jeff Nightbyrd, "Abbie Talks Before Vanishing," Village Voice, Hoffman is angered at Playboy for "blowing his cover"; 5. Abbie Hoffman, "I remember Papa," Boston Evening Globe, reflections on the death of his father; 6. Wendy Schwartz, "'Love Underground'," The Progressive, review of To America With Love: Letters from the Underground.] (Box 8:183)
  - News, 1977, [1. Sunday Telegram April 24th 1977, Living Section; 2. Larry Goldberg, n/a, The Crawdaddy, letter to the editor about Brandeis and Hoffman; 3. Jerry Rubin, "My Hope for America," Playboy, reflections on the 1976 Presidental elections; 4. Jacksonville Journal August 30th 1977, Accent on Family & Health section; 5. unknown, "After plastic surgery and three years on the run, Abbie Hoffman has tired of the chase," People, Hoffman reflects on the strain of the underground.] (Box 8:184)